There are so many people
هناك الكثير من الناس
who can't see clearly.
الذين لا يستطيعون الرؤية بوضوح.
There are so many ill-sighted youngsters
هناك الكثير من الشباب ضعاف البصر
at the foot of the mountain.
عند سفح الجبل.
You can use a small map to observe the number of enemies.
يمكنك استخدام خريطة صغيرة لمراقبة عدد الأعداء.
Ah,
آه،
There are more than 1000 people.
هناك أكثر من 1000 شخص.
What?
ماذا؟
Master, you have good eyesight.
سيدي ، لديك بصر جيد.
Do you have any solutions?
هل لديك أي حلول؟
What are you afraid of?
من ماذا انت خائف؟
Fight with them.
حارب معهم.
Yes.
نعم.
Fight with them for speed.
حارب معهم من أجل السرعة.
It's not too late for us to run.
لم يفت الأوان بعد على الجري.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخافوا.
Trigger a new task.
بدء مهمة جديدة.
If you defend Toad Village ten times
إذا دافعت عن قرية العلجوم عشر مرات
and run away, you'll be killed by me.
وتهرب ، سوف أقتلك من قبلي.
What?
ماذا؟
Who are you
من أنت
talking to again?
أتحدث مرة أخرى؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
What should we do?
ماذا علينا ان نفعل؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
What are you afraid of?
من ماذا انت خائف؟
It's that kid.
إنه ذلك الطفل.
Isn't he from Black Rock City?
أليس كذلك من بلاك روك سيتي؟
Is he dead?
هل هو ميت؟
For the brothers of Toad Village,
لأخوة قرية العلجوم ،
we can only use this idiot.
يمكننا فقط استخدام هذا الأحمق.
I found a way to defeat the enemy.
لقد وجدت طريقة لهزيمة العدو.
You thieves,
أيها اللصوص
today it falls into your hands,
اليوم يقع بين يديك ،
If you want to kill him or cut him,
إذا كنت تريد قتله أو قطعه ،
do as you please.
تفعل كما يحلو لك.
No!
لا!
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Don't regret it.
لا تندم.
Isn't releasing him today
لم يطلق سراحه اليوم
releasing the tiger back to the mountain?
تحرير النمر وإعادته إلى الجبل؟
What are you afraid of?
من ماذا انت خائف؟
Isn't he just a defeated opponent?
أليس هو مجرد خصم مهزوم؟
Does he dare to come back for revenge?
هل يجرؤ على العودة للانتقام؟
Oh,
أوه،
I thought,
اعتقدت،
He has a little bit of dignity as a warrior.
لديه القليل من الكرامة كمحارب.
I didn't expect that,
لم أتوقع ذلك ،
He slipped away with his tail between his legs.
انزلق بعيدا وذيله بين رجليه.
I am Lin Shaoyu from Canghai.
أنا لين شاويو من كانغهاي.
I'm here to challenge you.
أنا هنا لأتحداك.
Oh,
أوه،
someone is going to attack Toad Village.
شخص ما سوف يهاجم قرية العلجوم.
So scary.
مخيف جدا.
Help!
يساعد!
Get him!
اجلبه!
That's great. It really works.
ذلك رائع.  إنها تعمل حقًا.
Hurry up.
أسرع - بسرعة.
Apply gold wound medicine to him.
ضع دواء الجرح الذهبي عليه.
Oh,
أوه،
you're amazing.
انت رائع.
It's no big deal. Let's have a drink.
ليس بالأمر الجلل.  لنشرب.
When are you going to teach me,
متى ستعلمني ،
a lowlife like me?
وضيع مثلي؟
I, Qin Man, punched just one
أنا ، تشين مان ، لكمت واحدة فقط
punch. Awesome.
لكمة.  مذهل.
Master,
يتقن،
I bet ten cents,
أراهن بعشرة سنتات ،
I'm sure he'll come back for revenge.
أنا متأكد من أنه سيعود للانتقام.
I'll bet you 20.
أراهن عليك 20.
He won't come back for sure.
لن يعود بالتأكيد.
I know this kind of person too well.
أنا أعرف هذا النوع من الأشخاص جيدًا.
If he fails once, he'll become a coward.
إذا فشل مرة ، سيصبح جبانًا.
Do you think he deserves to be a warrior?
هل تعتقد أنه يستحق أن يكون محاربًا؟
I am Lin Shaoyu from Canghai.
أنا لين شاويو من كانغهاي.
I'm here to challenge you.
أنا هنا لأتحداك.
Oh,
أوه،
it's the second time someone has attacked Toad Village,
إنها المرة الثانية التي يهاجم فيها شخص ما قرية العلجوم ،
I'm scared again.
أنا خائف مرة أخرى.
Gosh, it's scary.
يا إلهي ، هذا مخيف.
Thank you for your hard work.
شكرا لعملكم الشاق.
I am Lin Shaoyu from Canghai.
أنا لين شاويو من كانغهاي.
I'm here to challenge you.
أنا هنا لأتحداك.
Newspaper,
جريدة،
Toad Village is right ahead,
قرية العلجوم أمامك مباشرة ،
Okay,
تمام،
I'm going to kill them.
سأقتلهم.
Newspaper,
جريدة،
The City Owner has an order
مالك المدينة لديه أمر
to return to the city immediately.
للعودة إلى المدينة على الفور.
What?
ماذا؟
Back to the city.
العودة إلى المدينة.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
the 1000 elite soldiers I sent to suppress bandits,
1000 جندي من النخبة أرسلتهم لقمع قطاع الطرق ،
Why are you summoned back urgently?
لماذا يتم استدعائك مرة أخرى بشكل عاجل؟
Of course it's because of an emergency.
بالطبع هذا بسبب حالة طارئة.